<resources>
    <string name="app_name">13033</string>
    <string name="action_Info">Info</string>
  <string name="Surname">Surname</string>
  <string name="action_Lang">Language</string>
  <string name="Name">Name</string>
  <string name="Address">Address</string>
  <string name="RememberSW">Remember inputs</string>
  <string name="SelectedText">Reason Selected:</string>
  <string name="ConfirmError">Oops... It seems like you have missed a field or forgot to choose your transportation reason. Please make sure you have everything correct.</string>
  <string name="Error">Error</string>
  <string name="OK">OK</string>

  <string name="InfoTitle">Abous Us</string>
  <string name="InfoMessage">This is an app created for people who are experiencing difficulties with technology and for elderly people whom we are trying to protect.\n\nNote that your data will be saved locally to your phone and will be deleted when you uninstall the application. In addition to that, data you provide will not be distributed to any Third Party applications or services.\nThe app is not making any internet connections and the only permission it requires is sms sending.\nThis app is NOT using GPS or any other tracking software, therefore it doesn\'t know where you are and what you are doing.\n\n\nYou can view the open source code with the updates on GitHub and there is also a video on youtube of me developing the app "How to make your own 13033 app (C# Xamarin Visual Studio)".\n\nCreated by Konstantinos Pap.\n\nNo Copyrights -- Open Source Project\n\n #stayhome #staysafe</string>
  <string name="Confirmation">Confirmation</string>
  <string name="Proceed">Proceed</string>
  <string name="Abort">Abort</string>
  <string name="Aborted">Aborted</string>
  <string name="SmsNotSupportedException">Not Supported</string>

  <string name="Attention">Attention</string>
  <string name="AttentionMessage">Please make sure that you have received an answer from 13033 to go out. Note that this message will be valid after the response from 13033</string>
  <string name="MessagesOverload">You are about to exceed the maximum amount of messages sent to 13033 within 24 hours. Are you sure you want to proceed? In case you don\'t receive a response from 13033 when you have exceeded the maximum amount of messages sent then the service has rejected your request and note that the application has nothing to do with it.</string>

  <string name="SmsFailed">Oops, something went wrong and your sms wasn\'t sent</string>

  <string name="AlertTitle">Do you wish to be alerted before the timer expires?</string>
  <string name="AlertMessage">Define how much time before SMS expiration you want to be alarmed</string>
  <string name="mins">Minutes</string>
  <string name="Hour">Hour</string>
  <string name="Left">Left</string>
</resources>
